# Ms. Anu Verma

- +66 0969458412
- anuverma48612@gmail.com
- Bangkok / Thailand

## ABOUT ME

Over 5 years of experience in Information Technology, Hospitality and E Commerce industry. VMware Taara Level 1 and Level 2 certified. Strong attention to detail and the ability to grasp new concepts and skills quickly. Looking for a role within a dynamic and growth-oriented company that will enable me to use my technical skills and leadership qualities and offer opportunities for career advancement.

# SKILLS

# 9 / 10 Microsoft Office

### 7/10

Minitab, SPSS

#### 9 / 10

Opera (Hotel PMS)

#### 7 / 10

SQL

#### 8/10

Data Analysis

## EDUCATION

Master's in business administration Alliance School of Business, Bangalore (India) 2012 – 2014 (80% CGPA)

### Bachelor of Technology

IMS Engineering College, Ghaziabad (India) 2004 – 2008 (71% CGPA)

## EXPERIENCE

### Sales Operation - Senior Associate

Zomato / Chennai, India / Sep 2016 – Feb 2018

- Working with restaurants partners on various marketing initiatives
- Analyzing territory wise restaurant performance of the city
- Placement or marketing ads, text, banners of Zomato website & app

### **Assistant Service Manager**

Vatika Business Centre / Chennai, India / Jan 2016 – Aug 2016

- Client office space management
- Daily operational responsibilities to have smooth operations
- Contracting new partners and renewal of existing partners

#### **Rooms Division Administrator**

Conrad Maldives (Hilton) / Maldives / Sep 2014 – Oct 2015

- Assist Front Office with their daily operational needs
- Analyzing guest preference before arrival and wedding arrangements

### **Project Engineer**

Wipro / Bangalore / Nov 2009 – July 2011

- Working for clients such as "Alliance" and "Capital one" on the coding for client data protection
- Development process on acquiring new credit card customers



VMware Certified Associate - Digital Business Transformation 2020



VMware vSphere 6.7 Foundations